## Clayton J. Lewis

2117 Rene Court. Apt. 2F Ridgewood, NY, 11385 775-233-7630 cjlewis07@yahoo.com

# **SUMMARY:**

I'm a technical professional that takes pride in having versatile knowledge in various software systems, operational workflows, and programming development. I've proven to be consistent in completing key projects in addition to making an influential contribution by applying my vast experience and incredible work ethic.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS AND ATTRIBUTES:

Software Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Linux CLI, WordPress, GitHub, AWS Cloud

Project Management Software: Jira, Trello, Wrike, WebEx, Slack

Computer Programs and Software: MacOS, Windows, Adobe Creative Suite, Microsoft Office, Google Drive

- Positive attitude with an enthused desire to learn.
- Powerful sense of urgency and detail in a professional work atmosphere.
- Passionate in providing excellence service to valued clients and customers.

## **EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS:**

### **Amazon Web Services**

Cloud Practitioner Certification- Jan 2021

### State University of New York College at Buffalo:

Bachelor of Arts, Media Production- May 2014

## **WORKING EXPERIENCE:**

### SeenThis- New York, NY

## **Technical Producer (07/2021 – Present)**

Producing high quality HTML5 Video Display Ads with the implementation of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript code within the SeenThis' CMS production platform. Utilizing Adobe Creative Suite to adjust digital brand assets for creative edits, custom exports and file size adjustment. Accurately following client brand style guidelines for digital ad campaigns and mockups. Providing technical production support for troubleshooting, display ad modifications, and client consultations. Working with the Tech, Product and Sales teams to optimize project production workloads and delivery services.

## Spectrum News NY1 - New York, NY Media Ingest Editor (07/2019- 07/2021)

Preforming with Dalet (MAM) software to record media by way of decoders and fiber feed lines in addition to the asset ingestion of video content from camera cards and third-party sources. Operating a Harris Router for delegated task such as quality control checks and distributing video content for Spectrum affiliates. Remotely coordinating live shows for shoot locations and IFB checks. Fulfilling auxiliary assignments such as segment replay cuts, video asset placement, archival restores and troubleshooting system malfunctions.

### **INTERNSHIPS:**

### **CHOYCES LLC**

# Web Design Intern (2021)

Updated CHOYCES website design with HTML and CSS code inside WordPress CMS Platform.

### **ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES:**

- Head Coach for North Park Hockey Organization (2021-Present)
- Head Coach for Ice Hockey in Harlem Program (2016- Present)
- Professional Line Cook (2013-2018)
- Buffalo State Bengals Men's NCAA Division III Hockey Team (2010-2014)